(thoughtful rock-ballad music)
♪ I'm standing on a bridge ♪
♪ I'm waiting in the dark ♪
♪ I thought that you'd be here by now ♪
♪ There's nothing but the rain ♪
♪ No footsteps on the ground ♪
♪ I'm listening but there's no sound ♪
♪ Isn't anyone trying to find me ♪
♪ Won't somebody come take me home ♪
♪ It's a damn cold night ♪
♪ Trying to figure out this life ♪
♪ Won't you take me by the hand ♪
♪ Take me somewhere new ♪
♪ I don't know who you are ♪
♪ But I, I'm with you ♪
♪ I'm with you ♪
♪ Hmm ♪
♪ I'm looking for a place ♪
♪ I'm searching for a face ♪
♪ Is anybody here I know ♪
♪ 'Cause nothing's going right ♪
♪ And everything's a mess ♪
♪ And no one likes to be alone ♪
♪ Isn't anyone trying to find me ♪
♪ Won't somebody come take me home ♪
♪ It's a damn cold night ♪
♪ Trying to figure out this life ♪
♪ Won't you take me by the hand ♪
♪ Take me somewhere new ♪
♪ I don't know who you are ♪
♪ But I, I'm with you ♪
♪ I'm with you, yeah ♪
♪ Oh, why is everything so confusing ♪
♪ Maybe I'm just out of my mind ♪
♪ Yeah-he-yeah, yeah-he-yeah,
yeah-he-yeah, yeah-he-yeah ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ It's a damn cold night ♪
♪ Trying to figure out this life ♪
♪ Won't you take me by the hand ♪
♪ Take me somewhere new ♪
♪ I don't know who you are ♪
♪ But I, I'm with you ♪
♪ I'm with you ♪
♪ Take me by the hand ♪
♪ Take me somewhere new ♪
♪ I don't know who you are ♪
♪ But I, I'm with you ♪
♪ I'm with you ♪
♪ Take me by the hand ♪
♪ Take me somewhere new ♪
♪ I don't know who you are ♪
♪ But I, I'm with you ♪
♪ Oh, I'm with you ♪
♪ I'm with you ♪